Jesse Engerman

Missouri City, TX 77459 jesseengerman@hotmail.com 8328687625

Jesse Engerman theexpandingpolytope.com

Web and Software developer with production experience and adeptness with managing high-end projects in deadline-oriented environments

Summary of Qualifications

Over 3 years Web and Software Development experience, with a strong background in successfully managing all levels of site development, from conception to deployment and management.

Ability to complete high-end projects in deadline-oriented environments.

Talented graphic designer with excellent problem-solving skills.

Able to clearly communicate ideas with a large number of employers and clients.

Design and Computer Skills

Languages: UI/UX, JavaScript, CSS, XML, HTML, ASP, SQL, PHP, C++, C#

Graphics/Engines: WebGL, OpenGL, GLSL, Unity, Unreal

Software: Git, vscode, vstudio

Work Experience

Software Engineer

Upwork freelancer March 2019 to Present

Building a browser horse simulation game, Last Stretch Home, using Bootstrap, Php, Laravel and MySQL.

Web Developer

Plant Site 3d - Katy, TX May 2018 to September 2018

Using HTML, Javascript, CSS, Three js and WebGL to help develop virtual 3D learning software for the oil and gas industry.

Education

High school or equivalent

Dulles High School - Sugar Land, TX 2012 to 2016

None in Pursuing Bachelor's in Computer Science

Skills

HTML (5 years), CSS (5 years), Javascript (5 years), WebGL (2 years), three js (2 years), Bootstrap (3 years), PHP (4 years), SQL (4 years), MongoDB (Less than 1 year), Node js (1 year), Jquery, Node, Wordpress, HTML 5, MySQL, Git

Links

http://www.theexpandingpolytope.com/

https://github.com/TheExpandingPolytope

Certifications/Licenses

Driver's License